var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "وَأَبَارِيقَ",
        "answer": "and jugs",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-abārīqa",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَآبَاؤُنَا",
        "answer": "And also our fathers",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "awaābāunā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْثِيمًا",
        "answer": "sinful (speech)",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "tathīman",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُجَاجًا",
        "answer": "salty",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ujājan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the later (people)",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the later people",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْآخِرِينَ",
        "answer": "and the later people",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "wal-ākhirīna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَئِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "a-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "415",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآكِلُونَ",
        "answer": "Will surely eat",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "laākilūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "520",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "521",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "1280",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "1281",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "664",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to him",
        "pcklId": "665",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "Then",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "And",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "wa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "the former (people)",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "the former people",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "the former",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُولَىٰ",
        "answer": "the first",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-ūlā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلُونَ",
        "answer": "former",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "l-awalūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْبَثًّا",
        "answer": "dispersing",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "munbathan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُبَدِّلَ",
        "answer": "We (will) change",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "nubaddila",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَارِدٍ",
        "answer": "cool",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "bāridin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبُسَّتِ",
        "answer": "And will be crumbled",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wabussati",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَسًّا",
        "answer": "(with awful) crumbling",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bassan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "you (do) not see",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "tub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبُطُونَ",
        "answer": "the bellies",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-buṭūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَبْعُوثُونَ",
        "answer": "surely be resurrected",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "lamabʿūthūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْكَارًا",
        "answer": "virgins",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "abkāran",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَغَتِ",
        "answer": "it reaches",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "balaghati",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَكُمُ",
        "answer": "among you",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "baynakumu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتْرَابًا",
        "answer": "equals in age",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "atrāban",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرَابًا",
        "answer": "dust",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "turāban",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتْرَفِينَ",
        "answer": "indulging in affluence",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mut'rafīna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَلَاثَةً",
        "answer": "three",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "thalāthatan",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُلَّةٌ",
        "answer": "A company",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "thullatun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُلَّةٌ",
        "answer": "A company",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "thullatun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَثُلَّةٌ",
        "answer": "And a company",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wathullatun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِبَالُ",
        "answer": "the mountains",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-jibālu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَحِيمٍ",
        "answer": "(in) Hellfire",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "jaḥīmin",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءً",
        "answer": "A reward",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "jazāan",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلْنَاهُنَّ",
        "answer": "And We have made them",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "fajaʿalnāhunna",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَجَعَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We (would) surely, make it",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "lajaʿalnāhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We (could) make it",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnāhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "have made it",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnāhā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَجْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "And you make",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "watajʿalūna",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَجْمُوعُونَ",
        "answer": "Surely, will be gathered",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "lamajmūʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتِ",
        "answer": "Gardens",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "jannāti",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَنَّتُ",
        "answer": "and a Garden",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "wajannatu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَدِيثِ",
        "answer": "statement",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-ḥadīthi",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْرُثُونَ",
        "answer": "you sow",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taḥruthūna",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَحْرُومُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) deprived",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "maḥrūmūna",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُطَامًا",
        "answer": "debris",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥuṭāman",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is the) truth",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُلْقُومَ",
        "answer": "the throat",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ḥul'qūma",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَمِيمٍ",
        "answer": "and scalding water",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "waḥamīmin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمِيمِ",
        "answer": "the scalding water",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamīmi",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمِيمٍ",
        "answer": "(the) scalding water",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ḥamīmin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْمُومٍ",
        "answer": "black smoke",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yaḥmūmin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحِنْثِ",
        "answer": "the sin",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ḥinthi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحُورٌ",
        "answer": "And fair ones",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "waḥūrun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينَئِذٍ",
        "answer": "(at) that time",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "ḥīna-idhin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَخْضُودٍ",
        "answer": "thornless",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "makhḍūdin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَافِضَةٌ",
        "answer": "Bringing down",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "khāfiḍatun",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخَلَّدُونَ",
        "answer": "immortal",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "mukhalladūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "[We] created you",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "khalaqnākum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْلُقُونَهُ",
        "answer": "who create it",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "takhluqūnahu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَالِقُونَ",
        "answer": "the Creators",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "l-khāliqūna",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَخَيَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "they select",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yatakhayyarūna",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدْهِنُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) indifferent",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "mud'hinūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "(of) Judgment",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَدِينِينَ",
        "answer": "to be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "madīnīna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "you take heed",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "tadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذْكِرَةً",
        "answer": "a reminder",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "tadhkiratan",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَرَأَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Do you see",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "afara-aytum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَرَأَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "And do you see",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "afara-aytum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَرَأَيْتُمُ",
        "answer": "Do you see",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "afara-aytumu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَرَأَيْتُمُ",
        "answer": "Do you see",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "afara-aytumu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "858",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "859",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "860",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُجَّتِ",
        "answer": "will be shaken",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "rujjati",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجًّا",
        "answer": "(with) a shaking",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "rajjan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْجِعُونَهَا",
        "answer": "Bring it back",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "tarjiʿūnahā",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your provision",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "riz'qakum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَافِعَةٌ",
        "answer": "raising up",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "rāfiʿatun",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْفُوعَةٍ",
        "answer": "raised",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "marfūʿatin",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَوْحٌ",
        "answer": "Then rest",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "farawḥun",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَيْحَانٌ",
        "answer": "and bounty",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "warayḥānun",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزْرَعُونَهُ",
        "answer": "cause it to grow",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tazraʿūnahu",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّارِعُونَ",
        "answer": "the Ones Who grow",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-zāriʿūna",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَقُّومٍ",
        "answer": "Zaqqum",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "zaqqūmin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجًا",
        "answer": "kinds",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "azwājan",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَبِّحْ",
        "answer": "So glorify",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "fasabbiḥ",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَبِّحْ",
        "answer": "So glorify",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "fasabbiḥ",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّابِقُونَ",
        "answer": "And the foremost",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wal-sābiqūna",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّابِقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the foremost",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-sābiqūna",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَسْبُوقِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) outrun",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "bimasbūqīna",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِدْرٍ",
        "answer": "lote trees",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sid'rin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُرُرٍ",
        "answer": "thrones",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "sururin",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْكُوبٍ",
        "answer": "poured forth",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "maskūbin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامًا",
        "answer": "Peace",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "salāman",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامًا",
        "answer": "Peace",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "salāman",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Then, peace",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "fasalāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "they will hear",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمُومٍ",
        "answer": "scorching fire",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "samūmin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاسْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "bi-is'mi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاسْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) name",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "bi-is'mi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْأَمَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the left",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-mashamati",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْأَمَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the left",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-mashamati",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَجَرٍ",
        "answer": "(the) tree",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "shajarin",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَجَرَتَهَا",
        "answer": "its tree",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "shajaratahā",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْرَبُونَ",
        "answer": "you drink",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tashrabūna",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرْبَ",
        "answer": "(as) drinking",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "shur'ba",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَشَارِبُونَ",
        "answer": "And drink",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "fashāribūna",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَشَارِبُونَ",
        "answer": "And will drink",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "fashāribūna",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "then why are you not grateful",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "tashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشِّمَالِ",
        "answer": "(of) the left",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-shimāli",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشِّمَالِ",
        "answer": "(of) the left",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-shimāli",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْتَهُونَ",
        "answer": "they desire",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yashtahūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "We willed",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "We willed",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "Then (the) companions",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "And (the) companions",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "And (the) companions",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "For (the) companions",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "li-aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "And (the) companions",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصَدَّعُونَ",
        "answer": "they will get headache",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuṣaddaʿūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُصَدِّقُونَ",
        "answer": "you admit the truth",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "tuṣaddiqūna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصِرُّونَ",
        "answer": "persisting",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yuṣirrūna",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَصْلِيَةُ",
        "answer": "And burning",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wataṣliyatu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّالُّونَ",
        "answer": "O those astray",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "l-ḍālūna",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّالِّينَ",
        "answer": "the astray",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "l-ḍālīna",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَلْحٍ",
        "answer": "And banana trees",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waṭalḥin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُطَهَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "the purified",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-muṭaharūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطُوفُ",
        "answer": "Will circulate",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yaṭūfu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "(of) fowls",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ṭayrin",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَظَلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "then you would remain",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "faẓaltum",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظِلٍّ",
        "answer": "And shade",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "waẓillin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظِلٍّ",
        "answer": "And a shade",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "waẓillin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُرُبًا",
        "answer": "Devoted",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ʿuruban",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Great",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Great",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmi",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِظَامًا",
        "answer": "and bones",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "waʿiẓāman",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmun",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "337",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمْتُمُ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "ʿalim'tumu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know ",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "542",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْلُومٍ",
        "answer": "well-known",
        "pcklId": "850",
        "tlit": "maʿlūmin",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِينٌ",
        "answer": "(with) large eyes",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ʿīnun",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعِينٍ",
        "answer": "a flowing stream",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "maʿīnin",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُغْرَمُونَ",
        "answer": "surely are laden with debt",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "lamugh'ramūna",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "not",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفُرُشٍ",
        "answer": "And (on) couches",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wafurushin",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفَكَّهُونَ",
        "answer": "wondering",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tafakkahūna",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَاكِهَةٍ",
        "answer": "And fruits",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wafākihatin",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَاكِهَةٍ",
        "answer": "And fruit",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wafākihatin",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "qabla",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَقَابِلِينَ",
        "answer": "facing each other",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "mutaqābilīna",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّرْنَا",
        "answer": "[We] have decreed",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "qaddarnā",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقُرْآنٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely, a Quran",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "laqur'ānun",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْرَبُ",
        "answer": "(are) nearer",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "aqrabu",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقَرَّبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the nearest ones",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-muqarabūna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقَرَّبِينَ",
        "answer": "those brought near",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-muqarabīna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُقْسِمُ",
        "answer": "I swear",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "uq'simu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَسَمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely an oath",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "laqasamun",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقْطُوعَةٍ",
        "answer": "limited",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "maqṭūʿatin",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَلِيلٌ",
        "answer": "And a few",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "waqalīlun",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "say",
        "pcklId": "1519",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1520",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلًا",
        "answer": "a saying",
        "pcklId": "1623",
        "tlit": "qīlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُقْوِينَ",
        "answer": "for the wayfarers in the desert",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "lil'muq'wīna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَأْسٍ",
        "answer": "and a cup",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wakasin",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٍ",
        "answer": "a Book",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "kitābin",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرَةٍ",
        "answer": "abundant",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "kathīratin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "answer": "deny",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "tukadhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاذِبَةٌ",
        "answer": "a denial",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "kādhibatun",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُكَذِّبُونَ",
        "answer": "the deniers",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "l-mukadhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُكَذِّبِينَ",
        "answer": "the deniers",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "l-mukadhibīna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِيمٌ",
        "answer": "noble",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "karīmun",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِيمٍ",
        "answer": "pleasant",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "karīmin",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكْنُونٍ",
        "answer": "well-guarded",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "maknūnin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَكْنُونِ",
        "answer": "well-protected",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-maknūni",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَكْوَابٍ",
        "answer": "With vessels",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bi-akwābin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَانَتْ",
        "answer": "So they become",
        "pcklId": "1245",
        "tlit": "fakānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "And you will become",
        "pcklId": "1246",
        "tlit": "wakuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used (to)",
        "pcklId": "1247",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "1248",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "And were",
        "pcklId": "1249",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "And they used (to)",
        "pcklId": "1250",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "and become",
        "pcklId": "1251",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "1252",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "1253",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he was",
        "pcklId": "1254",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he was",
        "pcklId": "1255",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he was",
        "pcklId": "1256",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللُّؤْلُؤِ",
        "answer": "pearls",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-lu'lu-i",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَحْمِ",
        "answer": "And (the) flesh",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "walaḥmi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَغْوًا",
        "answer": "vain talk",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "laghwan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Not",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَتَاعًا",
        "answer": "and a provision",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "wamatāʿan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَأَمْثَالِ",
        "answer": "Like",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "ka-amthāli",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْثَالَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your likeness[es]",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "amthālakum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَمْدُودٍ",
        "answer": "extended",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "mamdūdin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُزْنِ",
        "answer": "the rain clouds",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-muz'ni",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمَسُّهُ",
        "answer": "touch it",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yamassuhu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَالِئُونَ",
        "answer": "Then will fill",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "famāliūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَمْنُوعَةٍ",
        "answer": "forbidden",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "mamnūʿatin",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُمْنُونَ",
        "answer": "you emit",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tum'nūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِتْنَا",
        "answer": "we die",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "mit'nā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَ",
        "answer": "the death",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "l-mawta",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَاءٍ",
        "answer": "And water",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wamāin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the water",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-māa",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّجُومِ",
        "answer": "(of) the stars",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-nujūmi",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْزِفُونَ",
        "answer": "they will get intoxicated",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yunzifūna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْتُمُوهُ",
        "answer": "who send it down",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "anzaltumūhu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُزُلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) their hospitality",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "nuzuluhum",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنُزُلٌ",
        "answer": "Then, hospitality",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "fanuzulun",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلٌ",
        "answer": "A Revelation",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "tanzīlun",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْزِلُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the Ones to send",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "l-munzilūna",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْشَأْنَاهُنَّ",
        "answer": "[We] have produced them",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "anshanāhunna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُنْشِئَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and produce you",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wanunshi-akum",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْشَأْتُمْ",
        "answer": "who produced",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "anshatum",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّشْأَةَ",
        "answer": "the creation",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-nashata",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِنْشَاءً",
        "answer": "(into) a creation",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "inshāan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْشِئُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the Producers",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-munshiūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنْضُودٍ",
        "answer": "layered",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "manḍūdin",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "look on",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "tanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّعِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) Pleasure",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "l-naʿīmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعِيمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) Pleasure",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "naʿīmin",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارَ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "l-nāra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَبَاءً",
        "answer": "dust particles",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "habāan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهِيمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the thirsty camels",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-hīmi",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُورُونَ",
        "answer": "you ignite",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tūrūna",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْضُونَةٍ",
        "answer": "decorated",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "mawḍūnatin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيقَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) appointment",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mīqāti",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَعَتِ",
        "answer": "occurs",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waqaʿati",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَوَاقِعِ",
        "answer": "by setting",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "bimawāqiʿi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِوَقْعَتِهَا",
        "answer": "at its occurrence",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "liwaqʿatihā",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَاقِعَةُ",
        "answer": "the Event",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-wāqiʿatu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَّكِئِينَ",
        "answer": "Reclining",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "muttakiīna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وِلْدَانٌ",
        "answer": "boys",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "wil'dānun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَقِينِ",
        "answer": "certain",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-yaqīni",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَيْمَنَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the right",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-maymanati",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَيْمَنَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the right",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-maymanati",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the right",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-yamīni",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the right",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-yamīni",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the right",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-yamīni",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the right",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-yamīni",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِينِ",
        "answer": "(of) the right",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-yamīni",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a Day",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "yawmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "56",
        "ayah": "56"
    }
]; 
export default words;